Come on out, first student!
[LOL]
[Everyone's dopamine level is maxed out]
Why are you laughing?
[Who made everyone laugh?]
[Beautiful ASA-lisa]
Isn't she beautiful?
Next!
Come on out, RORA!
[LOL x2]
Does anyone need tissue?
[Why have they become Mona Lisa & tissue?]
Do you understand how scary it is now?
[The Silence of IDOL:
BABYMONSTER]
[Night has arrived
after a hectic schedule]
Now that we took a shower,
I want to go to bed.
[The schedule of the retreat was crazy]
Right?
I'm so sleepy.
I'm going to sleep now. I'm sleepy.
Isn't this bed too small?
I don't think the seven of us can sleep here.
I should sleep on the floor.
[Flop]
I'll just sleep here.
[Knock knock]
[Someone is at the door]
Who can it be?
- Who is this?
- A ghost?
[Did anyone order anything?]
[LOL]
[An extra mattress has arrived]
Here's your mattress.
Can you give me some space?
Your Korean is very good-yo!
[So hiphop]
Okay. I'll get going then.
[Everyone panics]
Wait. Are you just leaving it here?
It's super easy so install it yourselves.
[Gotcha]
Okay.
- Okay. Bye.
- Thank you.
[Start to work on it]
We're just like the kids at a retreat.
[Playfulness also starts]
Hold the ends.
[Tight 1 / Tight 2]
Hold them.
[I'll pull RAMI]
[It's become a game of pulling RAMI]
[The matress is out in no time]
It's like gimbap.
[Just by cutting the wrapper]
Let's go.
Oh, cool!
[Good job, RAMI]
I did it!
[The mattress inflates by itself]
[Peekaboo]
[#Mattress #Installation #Success]
But since
it (the mattress) is wrapped airtight,
all we needed to do was take it out.
- Exactly.
- How convenient.
It just takes one person to do it.
[Suddenly everyone wants to dive in]
Take a seat.
[They found their favorite bed here]
I love it.
We can sleep here.
[Now that the bed is here, it's time to sleep]
Here...
[Rummaging through]
[Someone hid a lemon candy here]
[Special item]
What is it? A candy?
[Everyone's eyes are on it]
What is it?
Who wants to have a candy?
[Everyone loves a candy]
Me?
We'll play a game to make it fair.
[A game? I'm down!]
A game?
['A bed battle' for a lemon candy]
[Push your competitor out of the bed
while sitting down!]
[The last one standing will be the winner]
[Chanting FOREVER as a cheer]
Here we go!
[The Bed Battle begins now]
This is...
I'm not up.
[Rolling]
Push her out!
Come here.
[RAMI took care of the two in a second]
[PHARITA is out too]
[RORA is scared]
[RORA backs down as a strategy]
Just quit.
[An easy win]
[The winner of the bed battle]
RAMI is the winner!
Congratulations.
[RAMI got the lemon candy]
My candy.
That was super fun.
[Whistle-!!!]
[Flying in the air]
Just what are you doing now?
What are you doing?
Aren't you the delivery guy?
[He seems familiar]
We've met, no?
He has two jobs.
[It's hard to make ends meet]
[LOL]
RAMI!
[Me..?]
What do you have in your hand?
Nothing.
I saw something yellow.
That's yellow.
Oh, my  hair?
Mine's yellow, too.
[LOL]
Not that. Give me that!
What happens if you eat a candy
before you go to bed?
It's yummy!
[I get that]
It is yummy.
Your teeth will rot.
No.
[Momentary pause]
I'm confiscating it.
He's confiscating it!
[Baby Florian]
I had this a lot when I was a baby.
Make sure you clean up your bed first
and go to sleep.
[Talent show D-DAY is tomorrow]
[Practice the dance move for the talent show!]
When I see you
practicing for the talent show,
I'll take that as you don't want to sleep,
[Sleeping item or Penalty item!]
so I'll make sure you fall asleep forever.
Everyone, go to sleep!
[After playing, everyone's all in bed]
This pillow is so comfy and cool.
Right?
I felt a bit hot while playing the game,
but I can feel myself cooling down.
This is great for hot weather.
It was so comfy that I dozed off for a bit.
I did, too.
It's so comfy.
[It's the best bedding item]
I want to take this home.
[Sitting up suddenly]
Hang on a second.
Wake up! Wake up!
[Everyone, wake up!]
Tomorrow is the talent show.
We shouldn't let the seniors students
beat us.
No way.
Let's go all the way.
[Talent show]
Let's practice hard and go to sleep.
I'll turn it on.
[Play]
Let me press 'play'.
[Rushing]
[Alright ok]
[BABYMONSTER]
(Avoiding the instructor) Should we turn off the music?
[Instructor, Say goodbye]
Let's be professional.
[Let me clap my hands professionally]
[Beep!]
[Somebody help BABYMONSTER]
[Rolling]
What's going on?
Are you sure you're asleep?
This won't do.
[Getting up]
It's cold.
- Are you cold?
- Yes.
[LOL]
Are you comfortable like that?
What's going on?
I guess you rolled out of your bed.
[Going back to bed, acting as if nothing happened]
[LOL]
Everyone, close your eyes.
[Standing right back up]
What are you doing still up?
Everyone's asleep.
Again.
[Practicing again, mimicking Instructor Florian]
It's me.
[I'm performing my part although it's hectic]
[Laser focused]
Come on.
Where's my partner?
[CHIQUITA is back]
[RAMI is guarding the door]
[RUKA's part is coming up]
Go dance!
[Guarding the door till the end]
[Hurry back]
[What you waiting for]
[Everyone is in sync]
Do it properly!
[Having fun mimicking Instructor]
What are you doing still up?
[Did you call me?]
[Hurry back]
What's with the door?
[Why can't I open it?]
Open it!
[LOL]
Get rid of this matress now!
Okay.
Who did this?
[LOL]
If there's any bed left...
There's none.
[Lying on the floor]
This won't do.
You're one team at this retreat.
You are a team.
Even if I catch just one of you,
you'll have to participate
in a group mission as a whole.
Everyone make a line!
1, 2, 3. Get up!
If you succeed in the group mission,
I'll get you an item
so you can sleep better.
That is, if you succeed.
But!
If you fail, you'll be given a penalty item.
Your group mission is to become a human fan.
The seven of you will have to pose
in the shape of a fan and stay that way.
Start now!
[Deciding the order first]
I'll go fourth.
- I'll go third.
- I'm good as long as I'm not the first.
That's the first.
The one here
must be strong.
That's not me.
[LOL]
[Who is the strongest baby?]
Who's the strongest?
[It's me]
CHIQUITA.
[Changed to CHIQUITA]
Lie down here.
[Human Fan]
Okay. Go!
You should go down more.
Everyone should depend on each other.
Why is it so far?
Okay. Come on.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Go on! Make the fan shape.
[AHYEON and CHIQUITA is a palm away]
Give me your hand.
Get up!
I'm sweating.
That was okay.
Although it wasn't perfect,
[I commend your effort]
it was okay as the first mission.
[Perfect angle]
Thank you. Salute!
Since you nailed the first mission,
I'll give you an item to sleep well.
Come forward, CHIQUITA and RAMI.
Yes, sir!
- It's an eye mask.
- How cute.
Thank you.
Wear it now.
Give me a cute pose.
I'm cute even if I'm not doing anything.
[LOL]
1, 2, 3.
[A sleeping fairy pose]
Good. That's it!
[Tapping]
Go to bed now!
I'll get going, then.
[LOL]
[Shh!]
Good night.
[Not really, get up!]
- Shall we practice again?
- Cool.
[Play]
CHIQUITA, you're at the center.
[FOREVER]
[LIKE I'MMA LIVE]
[BABYMONSTER]
[I'm that nice]
[What do you think makes us different?]
RURU! Slay it!
[Even cheeky RUKA pulls off her part perfectly]]
[Whistle---!]
[Total chaos]
BOUT IT BOUT IT
I'm feeling the rhythm all over.
[Annoyed meter is going up]
Everybody get down
[Nothing can stop me from dancing here]
My head is about to explode.
[LOL]
I can't take it anymore.
Here comes your second group mission.
Your group mission is called 'Cheek-to-cheek',
You'll be paired with your eyes closed.
In 20 seconds, you have to guess what it is
between your cheeks.
What's the first item?
- What's this?
- Get closer.
[The first answer: A shower ball]
Good.
A scrunchie?
A sock?
A slipper?
[A slipper? Really?]
You've used half the time.
The time is almost up.
Squishy.
- A humidifier?
- A doll?
[Five seconds left]
5, 4, 3, 2, 1
[The end]
Take it out.
What do you think it is?
Say it now.
[Will they say the correct answer?]
RORA's sleeping socks?
[She refused to give them]
I don't give out my sleeping socks.
[LOL]
Is that why it smelled?
It didn't smell!
It wasn't a sock.
- What is it?
- You can get it right.
A scrubber?
You keep saying scrubber.
The answer is...
A shower ball.
[Isn't it a scrubber for humans?]
It is a scrubber.
There's no sock like this.
[A creative but wrong answer]
The next team should close their eyes, too.
[The second item is an abacus]
Start now!
[Difficult]
You have to put your weight into it.
She's adjusting to RUKA's height.
What is it?
[Gently rubbing the cheeks]
There height isn't compatible.
What do you think it is?
[Ten seconds have gone]
You've used half the time.
Ten seconds have gone.
Is this some type of a musical instrument?
You're not that far off.
Not far off?
[Count down to five seconds!]
Last five seconds.
5, 4, 3
[This is hard]
2 , 1
[Will they figure it out?]
What do you think it is?
[Looking around]
What is it?
[Whisper is heard from somewhere]
MATH
[Rolling]
"Soroban"?
She got it in Japanese.
In Japanese, it's called "soroban".
I don't speak Japanese. Help me.
We call it "jupan" in Korean.
Correct.
[Yay! Correct!]
How did you know?
Do you know what this is?
- No.
- I do.
Do you know what it is?
[She was born in 2002, and she knows what it is]
You use it to solve math problems.
[The third item]
Let's start now!
[Game start!]
[They hate it already]
It's not there yet.
It's soft, isn't it?
Where are you going?
[LOL]
[Return]
Where are you going?
Think carefully.
Ten seconds have passed.
You have ten seconds.
Isn't this the scrub?
[Focused]
Isn't it a scrub?
5, 4
- I don't know!
- 3, 2, 1. Done!
I'll give you the chance to say the answer.
[LOL]
SHEESH
It used to be your part.
['SHEESH' out of the blue?]
[The key choreography of 'SHEESH']
[Kicking 'jegi']
[Thinking hard / What is it?]
I'll give you three seconds.
[Will they get it right?]
1, 2, 3
[SHEESH...?]
You failed!
You have to finish that sentence.
No. Time's up.
Don't you know what it is?
CHIQUITA doesn't know.
[You're a Korean]
You used to say that a lot.
Our 'jegi' dance.
[What a shame]
How disappointing.
- That's the way you kick 'jegi'.
- Really?
[RUKA is the only one who got it right]
Since RUKA got it right,
you'll choose two students who will
get the penalty item.
[Hmm]
[You]
[Who?]
[RORA]
Who else didn't do a good job?
[RAMI VS ASA]
ASA.
[ASA was doing well]
I did well.
[RUKA picked ASA]
RORA and ASA.
[RORA and ASA got picked for the penalty item]
We're ROSA.
RORA and ASA,
come follow me.
What?
We're going to hell.
What? I'm scared.
WELCOME TO HELL
[The instructor came back]
You will not
recognize your dear friends.
[Already funny]
[LOL]
Come on out, first student!
[LOOOOL]
[Everyone's dopamine level is maxed out]
It's an art piece.
Why are you laughing?
[Transformed into Mona Lisa]
Isn't she beautiful?
[Beautiful ASA-lisa]
You look good.
ASA-lisa.
Move your arms.
[Say hi]
Good.
This is my favorite outfit.
[Cute]
Next student!
Come on out, RORA!
[Burst out laughing]
Does anyone need tissue?
Your outfit is comfortable, right?
[Embossed tissue costume]
Right?
Very flexible too.
Have you realized just how scary I can be?
[Yes and no]
Go back to bed quietly.
Go to sleep!
Go!
[Falling on her back]
Good. Cover her with your tissue.
[Tissue blanket]
Good.
You're sleeping well.
[Abruptly]
This is hilarious.
Get up, tissue.
[Mona Lisa is up too]
[ASA-lisa PLAY]
She looks like fried tofu from the back.
[ASA-lisa's turn]
Here it comes.
[ASA-lisa's explosive rap]
[will bring tears to da Vinci]
[Hehe]
[With ASA-lisa & Tissue RORA
BABYMONSTER dances under the moonlight]
It must be so uncomfortable.
Come at the back.
[It's AHYEON's turn]
[It's hard to focus]
[Twitching]
[Don't think I'm ASA]
[The instructor comes again]
[Dance with us]
No way.
RORA.
[Hesitant]
I'm tissue.
Tissue?
[Opening the tissue]
Why are you here?
[I like Tissue RORA]
Come out now!
Look how other model students
[Pretending]
are sleeping soundly.
Go back to sleep.
[Standing back up]
[Lie down again]
[BABYMONSTER decides to take a revenge
on the instructor]
We have to take a revenge.
When he comes back,
shall we just stay still, not sleeping?
We could admire Mona Lisa.
Good.
You can use the tissue if you get teary.
[Practicing again, with the will to revenge]
[I can see the bright horizon]
Prepare to admire Mona Lisa.
[Overcoming the fear of the instructor]
[Here he comes]
[Everyone is in the art gallery]
[It's like they're at Louvre]
[This is the stone Louvre]
How beautiful.
[Even the instructor loves ASA-lisa]
But this is not the time
to admire this beautiful piece of art.
It's time for you to sleep.
Lie down!
Lie down?
[Okay, we will]
Lie down!
[Flustered]
In bed.
Sleep in your beds!
Tissue! Go lie down.
[Flop]
[Time for the tissue to go to bed]
[Now that we managed to tease the instructor]
[shall we practice again?]
Shall I practice, taking this costume off?
(Instructor is scary) Do it secretly.
[Hypnotized by her hand gesture]
Let's go!
[We forever forever]
[FOREVER EVER EVER]
[We're almost there!]
[The dance practice is about to hit the peak]
[Don't think we'll go to sleep, Instructor]
[Passionate BABYMONSTER never stops practicing]
[My passion to put you in bed is no joke]
Let's dance together.
I'll make sure you sleep forever.
What's going on?
Everyone quiet!
I can't take this no more.
I'll give you the hardest mission.
[No]
You must put the rings around my horns.
I'll run around and you'll have to put
the rings on my horns.
If you manage to put 20 rings
within a minute, you're good.
[Game start!]
[BABYMONSTER run after him straight away]
[Help me]
No! Don't come near me!
EASY PEASY~
[Let's all put them around the horns]
[The girls are having fun teasing the instructor]
No!
You shouldn't hold my horns.
30 seconds have passed.
[They're just having fun]
You can't put your head down suddenly.
[It's up to me]
Last ten seconds!
No.
[What a hectic ending]
Hold on!
This isn't right.
You kept touching the horns that they're broken.
They are not!
[Mission to put rings around the horns failed]
Did we fail?
Now, I'm going to give
a very special penalty item to RUKA.
Ta-da!
We have a new friend.
[What?]
[LOL]
She's from somewhere very far.
Come on out, RUKA.
[What the heck?]
So cute.
[It was good that they failed the last mission]
[It's like RUKA was born this way]
You'll sleep like this.
It suits RUKA so well.
Act like the alien is kidnapping you.
Like this?
I finally got RUKA!
[LOL]
No more practicing!
Sleep with your alien friend
till the morning comes.
You should use the mattress by yourself.
[Flops]
[Pfft]
[LOL]
[RUKA & the alien made the instructor laugh]
RUKA, at least take
your shoes off and go to sleep.
[Come on]
[Chaos]
The instructor is laughing.
[Now that it's sorted]
"They are sleeping well~"
[Standing up]
[Acting different to their words]
[The girls have no intention of sleeping]
[Standing up by the help of others.]
It's okay.
My alien friend hasn't eaten.
He's gone.
He's dead.
Bring him back to life.
[Let's practice and save your friend]
[FOREVER]
[Unification of humans and the alien by dancing]
[BABYMONSTER and the alien are having fun]
[She fell down after laughing too hard]
[FOREVER]
[Kiss]
[Practice for the talent show is over]
We were perfect.
- Perfect.
- That's right.
I guess the alien wants to take a rest.
[Is that so?]
He says it was tiring.
Let's go to sleep.
[Finally, the girls go to bed]
[I'm here, too!]
Good night.
Bye.
[Good night, everyone]
[Please look forward to the full version
of BABYMONSTER sleeping]
[With the familiar sound]
[Here comes the instructor]
Get up, everyone!
Everyone, up!
Yes, sir.
Did you sleep well with the Greenie?
Greenie is sick.
[Crumpled]
Why has he gone so flat?
[Out of nowhere]
He's sick because of you.
[Whatever]
Get up!
It's time for the talent show.
Right!
Today is the talent show.
[Let's slay the stage, Greenie!]
Get up!
We shouldn't let the senior students
to walk all over us.
[Let's go, BABYMONSTER!]
Let's go slay the stage.
Greenie should go to the ER.
Greenie is dead.
Bye.
Do you know there's a fan meeting in Seoul
in August?
- Whose?
- BABYMONSTER.
BABYMONSTER?
I know!
We're performing 'FOREVER'
by BABYMONSTER tomorrow.
Will we get to listen to them performing live?
Probably?